唉 我刚刚见了我的逃难搭档
Oh, man, I just met my evacuation partner.
绝对呆瓜一个
Total derf.
真糟糕 我只能和那个
Sucks that I can't take you
无聊到爆炸又没长屁股的家伙走了
instead of his boring, flat ass.
31827号 安静 以及按你最上面的那个按钮
Number 31827, be quiet! Also, button your top button.
但我这样看起来更酷
But I look way cooler this way.
从众才是酷
Conformity is cool!
从众才是酷 从众才是酷
Conformity is cool, conformity is cool,
从众才是酷
conformity is cool.
没错 杰西 你选香草味没错
Yes, Jesse, your choice of vanilla is fine
也不是只给小孩子吃的
and not for babies.
不对 你不能... 等下 你成功了
No, you can't... wait, you did it.
爱莎 分析话中的恶意成分
Aisha, analyze malice.
没有检测到恶意成分
No malice detected.
- 我成功了 - 恭喜呀 洋洋乐
- I did it. - Congratulations, Yumyulack.
为了奖励你的辛苦练习
For all your hard work, I'd like to reward you